# Stjepan Grgić

# Digital Product Designer

grgic.stjepan@gmail.com | +44 7732 877 679 | Moving to London stjepangrgic.com | linkedin.com/in/stjepangrgic

Summary –

Analytical and creative designer with over six years of experience in both startups and advertising agencies looking to join a challenging position with the ability to have ownership, responsibility and grow as a professional and as a person.

Work Experience -

Sabbatical / Travel break | January 2019 - August 2019

**OptimoRoute** | optimoroute.com

Lead UI/UX Designer | July 2017 - January 2019 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Worked on improving the experience of existing tools to enable businesses to run planing and delivery optimisations more efficiently.
- Involved in creating and designing the user experience and interface of new product features (Real-time Order Tracking, Customer notifications, Delivery breadcrumbs) from the ground up.
- Lead design projects (landing pages, marketing campaigns, presentations, sales collateral) for the OptimoRoute marketing and sales team

Axilis | axilis.com

Lead UI/UX Designer | March 2017 - July 2017 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Lead design of a healthcare SaaS product for the US based client. That included design and experience of Android based tablet and phone applications as well as an admin web application.
- Designed company website.

## **Underlayer**

Founder & Digital Product Designer | December 2015 - July 2017 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Personal design studio.
- Lead user experience and user interfaces design for multiple projects, some of which are:
  - Agrivi | stjepangrgic.com/work/agrivi (case study)
  - Memgraph | memgraph.com
  - HCV Dnevnik (iOS App) | App store link
  - TalkBook | talkbook.co

**Vibby** | vibby.com | stjepangrgic.com/work/vibby (case study)

Product Designer | March 2015 - January 2016 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Responsible for designing user experience and interface of every aspect of the product video player, 'vib' creation process, profiles, dashboard, explore page...
- Created countless wireframes and interactive prototypes.
- Involved in frontend development and 'sliced' online player, as well as the majority of other features of the web application.
- Designed new branding, presentations for investors, business cards, shirts ...

Summary of skills

- Advanced skills using design tools such as:
   Sketch, Photoshop, Ilustrator, Figma
- Prototyping and UX tools:
   InVision, OmniGraffle, Axure
- Proficient with 'slicing' designs using HTML and CSS
- Confident with: JavaScript (Vue.js, Gatsby.js), Git, Terminal After Effects Animation
- Other:
   Sketching, Drawing, Photography

Personal Skills

- Critical thinker
- Problem solver
- Good Listener
- Open-Minded
- Ability to adapt to multicultural environments
- Attention to details

Languages

- Croatian Native proficiency
- English Professional working proficiency
- German Elementary proficiency

Hobbies / In free time

- Reading as much as possible
- Photography
- Drawing and Painting

## **Grey Zagreb** | grey.com/croatia

Digital Designer | July 2014 - March 2015 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Worked on a wide range of advertising campaigns for clients like Microsoft, Erste Bank Croatia, A1 Telekom Austria Group and Croatian National Tourist Board
- Featured projects:
  - Share Istria | Istrian Tourist Board | <a href="mailto:stjepangrgic.com/work/share-istria">stjepangrgic.com/work/share-istria</a> (case study)
  - Vip Xmas Chat | A1 Telekom | stjepangrgic.com/work/vip-xmass-chat (case study)

## $\textbf{Virtus dizajn} \mid \underline{\text{virtus-dizajn.com}}$

Junior Web Designer & Developer | September 2013 - April 2014 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Designed websites for various local small business.
- Converted designs to HTML and CSS pages.
  - www.alati.info
  - www.liderizalidere.eu/hr/
  - www.bazeni-jerkic.com
  - www.klimaexpert.hr

#### Točka | tocka.co

Junior designer | September 2013 – April 2014 | Požega, Croatia

- Assisted the team in various design projects.
- I Designed a technical manual book for C-DESIGN Fashion software for a local textile design school.

Education		
Luucation		

## University of Zagreb, Faculty of Graphic Arts

Bachelor of Arts - BA (Dropout) | grf.unizg.hr/en/ | 2010 - 2013 | Zagreb, Croatia

Other training / online courses	
---------------------------------	--

### Coursera

- Gamification, University of Pennsylvania
- Introduction to Psychology, University of Toronto
- Interaction Design Specialization, University of California San Diego

### **Other**

I have gone through many courses from Lynda.com, SkillShare, TutsPlus, DigitalTutors ...